Preliminary Guide to the Alpheus Augustus Hurst Papers, 1816-1950
Alpheus Augustus Hurst papers 1816-1950
Hurst, Alpheus Augustus
1340 Items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Alpheus Augustus Hurst Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 1957.
Biographical Note
Alabama judge.
Collection Overview
Ledgers (hard back and composition book), legal documents, family correspondence, almanacs, advertisements, and pamphlets.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Hurst, Alpheus Augustus
Judges -- Alabama
Ledgers
Contents of Collection
- Accessions 56-372, 56-399
  - Contents of Box 1: (Box 1)
    - Legal Papers, 1825-1900s
    - Legal Papers, 1910-1928
  - Contents of Box 2: (Box 2)
    - Letters, 1816-1900
    - Letters, 1901-1950
  - Contents of Box 3: (Box 3)
    - Miscellany, 1880-1928
    - Bills and Receipts, 1818-1890s
    - Bills and Receipts, 1900-1928
    - Printed Material, 1879-1935
  - Contents of Box 4: (Box 4)
    - Volumes (23)
  - Miscellaneous Oversize Material (Opaperfolder 1)